- Have a brilliant day.
- Yeah, thank you.
You too.
Morning. What can I get you?
- Where's curly-hair lady?
- Sara?
She's out sick. Or at least,
- that's what she says.
- Oh.
She's got a new boyfriend.
What can I get you?
Usually it's my usual
and she usually has it ready
because I'm usually late.
Well, don't keep me in suspense.
Um, it's a PB and BRHC
on a roll.
Okay, so...
- "PB" would be peanut butter, I'm assuming?
- Yes.
"BR," bananas, raisins. "H,"
honey. "C," cheese on a roll.
Aren't you blessed
with a fast metabolism.
Are you running a marathon
or something?
You know, my sister ran a marathon once,
God rest her soul.
She's not dead.
She's just exhausted.
We get it, Sharon. You ran.
But everyone has to work
in the morning.
Yeah, I have to go to work,
three minutes ago.
And, sorry,
I'm in sort of a rush for the sandwich.
You can't
rush a good sandwich, dude.
Alfred, really can't talk.
Good morning, Mr. Allen.
No, I'm late.
And I'm starving,
and curly-haired girl isn't here
and her name is Sara,
and she has a boyfriend.
We have a situation
at Gotham General.
A robbery gone wrong.
This is
the middle of the morning.
Why is our bat-friend
even awake?
Call Superman.
That was my first thought.
Sadly, he's otherwise engaged.
- Active volcano in Central America.
- Classic.
What about Diana?
My other first thought.
Rather annoyingly,
she's not picking up.
How many first thoughts, exactly, did
you have before you first thought of me?
Never about her.
- This is about you.
- Hi, sorry. Is my sandwich...
I learned my lesson
on the boat last year.
Stuff my sister comes out with
when she's drunk.
Personal comments about
my mom's friends as well,
which I think
is what I say about her...
Oh, my God!
Flash!
- Hi. Thank you.
- I love you.
- You seem very nice also.
- Oh, my God!
- No way!
- I think I'm gonna die!
Patching you into Mr. Wayne.
No, please don't.
Oh, my God.
Sorry if this sounds weird,
but are you actively eating that candy bar?
Maybe you could throw it to me?
- In the name of justice.
- Yes, yes.
I need you here now, Barry.
Hi, Bruce. Yes, I'm...
coming.
♪ Spirit like
A rumblin' train ♪
♪ Spirit of
The thunderin' rain ♪
♪ Vibrations got you
On the run ♪
♪ Electric child on bad fun ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
No!
No, no!
Bruce, this is a huge mess.
Why aren't you here?
Bruce, why does
it sound like you're fleeing the scene?
Falcone's idiot kid decided to
try to play in the big leagues.
He put a crew together and broke
into the lab at Gotham General.
Stole a highly deadly virus.
I intercepted them,
but they blasted their way out.
You can handle the hospital,
Barry.
Somebody has to save the rest of the world,
so I was gonna do that.
If you don't mind.
Sounds about right, Bruce.
"Thanks for saving me
from the sinkhole, Flash."
Barry, gas
and water pipes ruptured.
In the basement.
Right.
On it.
Can you open it?
- I think it's locked.
- It's jammed.
God, it's not working!
Oh, please!
Look, Alfred.
I've come to accept
that I'm essentially the
janitor of the Justice League.
Which sucks.
But I've come to accept it.
But...
I can't help but notice...
that it always seems to be
a bat-mess...
that I'm cleaning up.
- Right this way. Eyes forward.
- Yes.
- Stay together, now.
- Yeah, I know, right?
Look out!
- Wow. Whoa.
- What?
If my calculations are correct,
and history will prove
they usually are,
the foundational damage is about to
cause the collapse of the east wing.
- East wing's fine.
- All right, I got you.
Which is good
because my speed is lagging.
Running on empty, Alfred.
Do you hear that?
That's my stomach.
No, no.
It's the collapsing east wing.
Barry, 30th floor.
There's a baby...
Shower.
Oh!
Mr. Allen,
you've made me very proud.
And a lot of mothers very happy.
Oh!
Yeah.
Okay.
I understand that these events
can be psychologically scarring.
You should seek the services
of a mental health professional.
The Justice League is not
very good at that part yet.
Trust me.
God.
Shake him off!
If that briefcase
falls into the water,
it could wipe out
half of Gotham by lunchtime.
- Damn it.
- Please don't drop me.
Oh, God, no.
Please, please don't.
No!
Sorry I'm late.
Watch your step.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Nice suit.
Looking good, Flash.
Oh, uh... Thank... Uh...
And you...
are welcome.
My ego's far too big to say
"thank you" to someone else.
Hmm.
I developed this...
all-powerful persona to compensate
for my childhood trauma...
I, too, have childhood trauma.
Batman seems crazy.
- The Lasso of Truth...
- Billion dollar. She's the mother...
never gets old.
I'd do a lot better
just giving all my money away.
Yes, if I really wanted to end crime,
I should end poverty.
I know sex exists.
I've just never experienced it.
Damn it.
Well...
I have to run.
Yeah.
Always a pleasure.
The sex thing was a metaphor...
for gothic literature.
There was just no way
to recover from that.
Just let it go.
Well, I'd really love to stay
and clean up more mess...
but this little superhero
needs his breakfast.
Goodbye, Flash.
Yeah. Bye, Batman.
Well done, Mr. Wayne.
Will you be home
for breakfast, sir?
Yes, I think so.
The road to destruction.
This was never about her.
This is about you.
You have to stop
living in the past.
Now, was that
fast enough for you?
Morning, professor...
Ah, look who's here.
Shut up, Albert.
Every day. I don't know
how you do it, Barry.
What'd you, like,
crawl here, bro?
- Is he mad?
- Well, you're getting fired.
- You're getting murdered.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Let me guess.
Your alarm clock didn't go off.
- No...
- Oh, your dog ate your alarm clock.
Your alarm clock ate your keys.
Your keys' grandmother died,
and they need a personal day.
- It was none of those things.
- What was it this time, Barry?
It was, um, something else
that was far less outlandish.
And I know
I missed the meeting...
but I'd still really like to present
these case files for potential review.
I think we rushed these cases.
- We need to reopen them.
- Oh! Rushed?
We got a backlog six months deep,
and you want us to move slower?
You need to focus your motion.
Do the work,
close the case, move on.
You have
a lot of potential, Barry.
You shouldn't still be getting
me coffee after all these years.
You're right. That's...
That's true.
Go get me a coffee.
- Two sugars? Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
You're gonna love this.
I'm very satisfied with the
ruling in the Johnson case.
The evidence our lab analyzed...
was more than sufficient
to be conclusive.
- I'm still working that evidence.
- Because of the diligence
and hard work and focus...
Barry was still working
on that evidence.
Think if it were up to you
that we'd still be scraping
Ted Bundy's molars.
You know what? I'm so happy
you find this all so hilarious,
but we are dealing with real
people's lives, people's families.
And I don't think you can grasp
the gravity of that.
So, why don't you
leave me alone?
- Barry Allen?
- Iris West.
You...
know my full name also.
Yes, from school.
Aw, Barry, you didn't tell us
you had a friend from school.
- We actually didn't know that Barry had a friend.
- Wow.
Yeah, what does that
make it now?
- One?
- One.
You guys are so...
Um, bye, you guys.
Okay. Oh, my God.
That was just...
Um...
They're not really my friends.
They're my work friends.
Do you work here?
Yes, I do.
God, it's been a long time, huh?
Hmm.
I feel like we saw each other...
like a few years ago, right?
No, because...
we haven't
seen each other since...
college.
Ah.
Maybe I was just
thinking about you.
Well, I'm really glad
I ran into you.
- Yeah.
Your father's appeal
is tomorrow, right?
Yeah. How...
Sorry, how do
you know about that?
I'm covering it for the paper.
Oh.
How is he holding up?
Um...
Are you asking for the paper?
- No, I'm asking as a friend.
- Oh.
Although I'm sure the public
would want to know as well.
Well...
my only official comment
is that my dad is innocent.
Right.
I mean, no one...
would want to believe that
their father killed their mother.
What do you mean, "believe"?
My dad shouldn't be in jail.
My mom should be alive.
It's not about what I believe.
- It's about what the truth is.
- Right. No, yes, that's...
Oh, my God.
That's what I meant.
Right.
Sorry,
I have no official comment at this time.
You have a collect call
from the
Iron Heights Penitentiary.
- Do you wish to accept?
- Yes.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, Barry.
- How ya doing?
- I'm fine.
- You getting out much?
- Yeah.
Well, no. Uh, no.
But I, um, I ran into
an old college friend...
Iris West, today.
Didn't you have
a monster crush on her?
Well, she have a boyfriend?
- Why don't you ask her out?
- Dad, I, um...
I had a friend run the old security
camera footage from the store...
through this new program
he's developed.
And it's crystal clear now.
It's just...
you never look up, Dad.
You can't see your face.
So, without new evidence
to support your alibi...
we're just gonna need to start
thinking about the next appeal.
No, uh-uh. You need to stop
worrying about your old man.
Do that, you might actually
have time for a girlfriend.
But Dad, I don't want...
We've done this before.
This was a last-ditch effort...
and we'll go through
the motions tomorrow.
I'm okay, really.
You know, sometimes I even think
it's probably easier for me to be in here
than out there...
without her.
'Cause this way,
I can imagine she's alive...
out there living her life.
Barry?
You there?
Yeah, I'm here, Dad.
Hey, remember that sauce
she'd make on Sundays?
The whole house would
smell like basil, tomatoes.
And she'd put on my sweats
and start singing.
Yeah, what was that song?
I loved that song.
Remember that part.
It's not fair.
What's not fair, Monkey?
This question is stupid.
How many calculations can
you think of with an answer of 24?
There are a bajillion answers.
How am I supposed
to fit them all?
You are right. There are a
bajillion answers to this question.
Not every problem
has a solution.
Sometimes you just
have to let go.
Give your brain a rest and help
me make the pasta. Come on.
No.
Henry?
I need you to do me a favor.
- I don't do favors.
- Okay.
Barry needs you
to do him a favor.
Oh, Barry! Yeah, anything.
I need another can of tomatoes.
You have a can of tomatoes.
I need another one.
I thought you guys
went to the store this morning.
But I forgot the tomatoes.
This looks way more fun.
Let's just let
Barry go to the store.
You drive, right, Squirm?
- What? No.
- Getting so big.
You can do anything.
Look at ya.
You're getting gray, actually.
- Green can, not the blue one, okay?
- Got it.
Blue can,
not the green one, right?
- No! Green can, not the blue one.
- What?
Oh, God.
She's gonna start singing. Run!
Run, Barry!
I love you, Monkey.
I love you more.
I loved you first.
Nora?
Barry!
Barry! Barry!
Call 911 now!
Barry?
Don't worry about tomorrow.
We always knew
it was a long shot...
Dad?
Your call with Iron
Heights Penitentiary has been terminated.
Barry Allen?
Evidence our lab...
You need to focus your motion.
Do the work...
She promised...
Now, was that
fast enough for you?
So, you're saying
you went back in time?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like in Pozharnov?
Yeah, like in Pozharnov, except,
but Pozharnov was a second.
This time
I went back a whole day.
So, let's imagine...
that it is, in fact, possible
for you to run...
faster than
the speed of light...
and in so doing,
travel back in time.
It still would be...
wildly irresponsible.
I knew you were gonna say this.
Yes, because, Barry,
if you were to go into the past,
any interaction you have
with your parents or yourself,
you step on
the wrong blade of grass,
you have no idea what the
consequences to that could be.
No, I know.
The butterfly effect, right?
- Yes.
- I get it. But Bruce...
I could fix things.
You could
also destroy everything.
I could save her.
I could save both of them. I...
I could save your parents.
Barry, these scars we have...
make us who we are.
We're not meant
to go back and fix them.
And there's nothing broken
with you that needs to be fixed.
Take it from an old guy
who's made a lot of mistakes.
Don't live your past.
Live your life.
Don't let your tragedy
define you.
What if it's supposed
to define me?
Your tragedy made you a hero.
And also made me alone.
We could hang out.
I mean, do you wanna get a bite?
Like, I'm still hungry.
Not this time.
Maybe some other time.
Yeah.
Nice ride.
You have fancy friends.
Yeah, it was an Uber.
Exec.
Look, Iris, I really can't
talk about the case at all.
I'm not here as a reporter.
Can we talk?
Come on in.
I'm not gonna lie. It's a lot
tidier in here than I expected.
- Yeah? Yeah, well, um...
- Yeah.
I'm a pretty tidy person.
- Can I offer you a drink?
- Sure.
I'll take a beer.
Hmm.
Beers, beers, beers.
I keep 'em in my fridge.
Thanks.
Sure.
Look, I feel really bad
about earlier.
I should've been more sensitive.
And, um, I probably
could've been less sensitive.
I mean, I can't imagine
what you've been through.
It's like you lost
both parents in one day.
I did.
I lost my mom to a tragedy,
and I lost my dad to the
failures of the justice system.
Is that why you got
into criminal forensics?
To try and fix the system?
Yeah.
Yeah, to fix it.
There's gotta be a way
to fix it, right?
I mean, that's kinda why
I got into journalism, too.
I could make it right if I
could just go back somehow
and warn them without them
knowing that I'd warned them.
I... thinking like that's
gonna...
Drive you crazy.
"If I could just
go back in time...
"and stop the guy
who did it." It's...
No, I can't do that,
'cause that's way too much interaction.
My dad wasn't even at home.
My mom sent him
to go get a can of tomatoes.
I think whoever broke into
the house thought it was empty.
And then my mom was in there
with the knife in her hand
and things went bad,
just this absurd
chain of events.
And it's like, this footage should've
finally supported my dad's alibi.
But instead...
three lives ruined
for a can of tomatoes.
Oh, my God.
What?
Well, that could be it.
If my mom doesn't forget
the tomatoes in the first place,
then he never leaves
and she never dies.
No one would even
have to see me.
Bruce said no interaction.
This is no interaction.
This is just quick in,
quick out,
back to the present,
like I was never even there.
That's how I fix it.
Oh, my God, Iris.
- Hmm?
- Thank you, so much.
- This has been great.
- Oh.
Um... I'm sorry.
I... I have to leave.
Okay. Right.
Uh...
I had a really great time,
by the way. We should do this again.
Kal-El, son of Krypton.
This is a bad idea.
So, you're fast.
Your dad's a murderer.
Call 911 now!
Now!
Hi, Mom.
Don't forget the tomatoes.
See you soon.
Please work.
♪ Happy Birthday, dear... ♪
Happy Birthday, Barry.
- Go, Barry, hurry up.
- Go!
Congratulations
to the class of 2013!
I love you so much.
Monkey!
What are you wearing?
Is that Barry?
And he's early?
What universe is this?
You've cut your hair.
Now you can see your eyes.
- You look terrible.
- Henry!
- You look old.
- You look beautiful, baby.
What are they doing to you
over there?
Leave him alone. He's perfect.
Come here.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
I love you more.
I loved you first.
Go take a shower and change.
You smell like a boot.
Go, go, go.
"Old," seriously?
Well, no, I mean like mature.
He's at that age,
he wants to look old.
He, you know,
gets into bars that way.
How can I help?
Mm. Hey, Mom,
how was your day?
How was your month,
or your last 18 years?
Or that's a weird question...
'cause I was here.
But obviously, we share
those memories together.
Or I don't know,
maybe we could make some new memories.
Like we could go to the aquarium,
or the circus,
or to the park and you
could push me on a swing.
That's also weird
because I'm an adult now,
so I'd probably motivate
my own motion on a swing.
So, how was it this week?
How's school?
At school was... is good.
- Mm.
- School's been great.
I've just been working
really hard there on my...
studies.
Did you ask out
that girl from econ?
I know freshman year is about
going out, meeting people, okay?
Exploring things.
Experimenting.
But you have to be very careful.
Oh, shit.
I... have to shit.
Outside.
Help!
Shh! Why are you here?
What year is it?
- No, no, no.
- Help!
That's my face.
You stole my face.
Think I'm having
a mushroom flashback?
- Is that a thing?
- How old are you?
Eighteen.
Whoa.
This is mad trippy.
So, we're, like, in the future.
No, wait.
This is not trippy, dude.
This is catastrophic.
And no, we're not in the future. I was
supposed to be back in the present,
but I'm still in the past.
And there's not
supposed to be two of me.
You and I are not supposed to
be occupying the same reality at all,
let alone interacting.
I just can't believe I'm a
superhero who time travels...
No, no, no.
You are not anything.
Which is good. You don't want
to be a superhero. It's scary.
And I get bug splatter
in my teeth all the time.
Awesome.
Hey, do the thing again.
No, we don't have time.
- Mom!
- Shh!
What are you doing?
You're gonna tattle now?
- Do the thing.
- Fine.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Happy?
Now undo it.
I can't, I can't.
Ow.
Barry, are you okay up there?
We're fine! I'm fine!
Okay, Monkey.
So, do you have like a plane
that goes underwater?
Or like a boat that can fly?
How old are you, like 40?
Okay, you don't stop talking.
It's not charming.
It's abrasive and exhausting.
And, oh, my God. I am starting
to realize what people mean.
Just...
do me a favor
and promise me that meeting me
isn't gonna screw up space-time.
Broski...
I got you.
Shit, I'm in so much trouble.
What do you mean?
What do I do?
I could drug you.
Yeah, I could drug you,
and then you'd pass out,
you'd wake up
and you'd forget
that anything ever happened.
And it wouldn't be wrong,
right? Because you're me.
No! I mean, we shouldn't.
- Please don't... drug me.
- No.
No. Because here's the thing,
and I thought about it before.
I don't want to be drugged.
But I'm sure
we can think of another way.
Let's put on
our Barry thinking caps
and think of
a different solution
for memory loss.
Also, I'm a green belt...
in the Capoeira,
and I have
extensively studied wrestler,
and I could just go
frickin' lunatic on you.
Besides,
I have a date tonight...
Okay.
How hard do you have to hit
someone to make them forget stuff?
If I hit you in the past,
will it hurt me in the future?
Wait. You say
you have a date tonight?
Yeah. Wait,
what were you doing?
Uh, nothing.
Who's your date with?
This super babe
in my econ class.
- Iris West?
- Oh, my God!
Do we marry her?
You're going on
a date with her tonight?
That's why
I need Mom to do my laundry.
You don't even
do your own laundry?
Do you?
Okay.
- I'm actually gonna go.
- What do you mean?
Enjoy your life. Do you.
Change literally nothing.
- Um, I'll see you again never.
- I have a few more questions, though.
We have so much
to learn from each other.
Oh, great.
Well, you're leaving me.
And now the storm's
gonna ruin my date.
What day is it today?
Uh... Uh...
Sunday?
No, the date.
It's September 29th.
Shit.
This storm, this is the day.
- What day?
- The day I got my powers.
The day you get your powers.
- Powers?
- Listen...
I can't tell you why
I traveled back in time,
and I can't tell you
what I changed.
But, essentially,
in my version of reality,
I ended up interning
at the Central City Crime Lab
in my freshman year,
and that's where it happened.
Well, happens.
Tonight, September 29,
the accident that gives me my powers.
And if you're not there...
in 30 minutes...
then you won't get the powers.
Which means
I don't get the powers, maybe?
And then, that would mean
that I lose my way
of getting back in time
in the first place,
and then I literally
have no idea what happens.
Powers?
Wait, but what about
our date tonight?
She might be our future wife.
There might not be a future...
if you don't come with me...
right now.
Eight minutes.
How are we gonna to get inside?
What are you doing?
Would you stop whining?
This is gonna feel kinda weird.
We walk through the door.
Yes, it's okay.
It's called phasing.
Come on.
I love phasing.
Uh-huh.
Everybody moves.
Well... this is it.
This is where I was sitting.
And actually,
let me take this for you.
Thank you.
Okay, I had just
opened those windows...
to clear out the fumes.
Right around now.
And I was sitting in that chair,
and I was right under
this shelf of chemicals.
And that's when
the lightning hits.
Wait.
- I get hit by lightning?
- No, no, no.
You don't get hit by lightning.
Okay, 'cause for a second
I thought you said...
The lightning
hits the chemicals...
which then you get bathed in,
- and that's what electrocutes you.
- Okay,
- but I don't want to be electrocuted, though.
- Sit down.
- No, you sit down.
- I already have the powers!
You already have the powers!
Exactly!
I am not getting
struck by lightning!
It worked.
It looks like you lost a tooth.
Oh.
- No?
- You lost a tooth.
All right. We gotta go.
What have we got?
The alarms in the sterile lab.
Go check it.
Securing the entrance.
We've gotta phase.
Phase, phasing.
Oh...
Shit!
I'm slow.
Oh. Oh.
Why is your place so much nicer
- than I expected it to be?
- You like it?
Mom had to help decorate.
You know Mom.
Right, yeah. Classic Mom.
Classic Mom.
Hmm.
- What a day.
- Barry,
the accident gave you powers,
but took mine away.
So, I don't know how I get back.
Without access
to the Speed Force,
I don't know how I ever leave.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
- I might be stuck.
- Wait.
I have powers now?
Yeah, but...
you... No, no, no.
Holy speed balls.
Okay, I know
this is incredibly exciting,
because I went through it.
Speedy Gonzales!
Yes, I've done it
many times myself.
You can't just start...
Shit.
♪ We are young, we run green ♪
♪ Keep our teeth
Nice and clean ♪
♪ See our friends
See the sights ♪
♪ And feel all right ♪
♪ Got some cash
Bought some wheels ♪
♪ Took it out
'Cross the fields ♪
♪ Lost control, hit a wall ♪
♪ But we're all right ♪
Oh, my...
Ahh!
Okay, I'm leaving!
Put your hands up.
What did you do?
Nothing. Why?
Barry...
I could've told you about
the clothes. It's friction.
You run too fast,
and regular fabrics are gonna burn up.
It's the same reason why you can't
move people very far at hyperspeed.
That broccoli looks rotten.
Look, some things you can move.
Like, you can move,
for instance, a microwave.
But you can't move
something like, say...
- a baby.
- Barry,
it's like I've never eaten
anything before.
Everything has this
vivid flavor. Try a little.
Just take a little bite.
That's bad, isn't it?
Yeah,
this is not good. No, I was kidding.
I'm amazing. We're amazing.
I'm so hungry.
Hey, wait.
I wanna try that phasing thing.
How do I do that?
You don't. Not yet.
Okay? It's very complicated.
Takes a long time to train
your body to be able to speed up
whilst your molecules slow
down enough to pass through
the molecular structure
of solid objects...
Get out of here!
You've gotta start letting me
finish my sentences.
Are we always this sleepy?
And hungry and naked?
Well, the first two, yes.
The third one, no.
I've figured that part out.
And honestly,
if we're gonna do this
there's a lot I'm gonna have to
explain to you.
So, a good place to start,
I guess,
is that, yeah, the original suit
was actually made out of this polysynth...
Or we'll
pick this up tomorrow.
So, the suit is inside the ring?
- Yeah.
- What?
And I can have this?
No, you can't have it.
You can borrow it
so you don't kill yourself
using your powers.
You're gonna push this button
and the silk molecules are gonna uncoil,
absorbing atmospheric gases
and expanding the suit
to full size.
Ready?
It was so tiny...
You're supposed to put it on
before it hits the floor.
What, like change...
right here in front of you?
There's no one even
here anyway, Barry. Come on...
- Whoo, man.
- Tight.
It hurts.
You know where it hurts?
- In my dick.
- Okay. I know, I know,
but I don't need to know.
- Sorry, can we move on?
- Mm-hmm.
Here's what I'm thinking.
If I can train you
to move like I do,
then we can re-create
the Chronobowl.
Chronobowl?
In the Speed Force.
Speed Force?
And then maybe we can find some
way to get me back to the future.
Back to the Future. Yes!
Eric Stoltz
is chur boy in that movie.
What an embodied performance.
You mean Michael J. Fox?
Back to the Future?
- Yeah, in the movie Back to the Future?
- Oh, my God!
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
You need to
take the suit off now.
Thank God.
Reported seeing
a mysterious object
hovering above
the Australian seaboard.
- We've obtained footage from the sighting...
- Zod.
- And as you can see, the object...
- "Zod"?
- Appears to be a flying ship of some sort.
- What's a zod?
According to
US government officials,
satellite data
has confirmed
the presence of a spacecraft.
We'll be sure...
My name is General Zod.
I come from a world
far from yours.
For some time, your world
- has sheltered - one of my citizens.
- No, no, no.
- This can't be happening.
- I request that - you return this individual...
- Not now.
- To my custody.
What's happening?
For reasons unknown...
Zod's looking for Superman.
What's a superman?
Superman is an alien
who lives on Earth.
I'm assuming still incognito.
But, yeah, he's an alien,
and he's very powerful,
and he's just the best.
And then Zod is an alien
from the same planet,
also very powerful,
but he's just the worst.
And Zod came here to find Clark.
- Wait, who's Clark?
- Clark is Superman.
- Oh. Okay.
- But then
Zod also tried to terraform the
planet with this World Engine thing,
and Superman
stopped him eventually,
but not before Zod killed
thousands of people.
- Yeesh.
- And at the time,
there was
nothing I could do, I've...
Wait, you...
You were there?
Yeah, I had just
gotten my powers.
And I was still putting some
finishing touches on my suit.
This thing, Zod's World Engine,
it started destroying Metropolis,
so I just went there
and I started
trying to save people.
Daddy?
Listen to me!
Run away!
There was this kid, and I...
I got him, but then...
I couldn't get his dad.
Daddy!
It was all I could do,
save that one kid.
Only Superman could stop Zod.
But not in time
to save those people.
And now
it's about to happen again.
But...
if I can find
the entire Justice League,
Superman and
the rest of the band...
Right.
Then maybe I can prevent
the whole thing
from ever even happening at all.
- Um, give me your laptop.
- Okay.
What is that smell?
Ugh. Could be anything.
Honestly.
Who's that?
Oh. That's Gary.
That's the smell. It's...
Don't worry. He's breezy.
We can do this.
Uh, let's see, Victor Stone,
Gotham City University.
Oh, this is my roommate, Patty.
Patty...
is your roommate?
And that's her boyfriend,
Albert.
What's up?
Good morning.
Oh, sorry. And, uh, guys...
This is my cousin.
Barry.
Whoa.
I'm starving.
Okay.
Victor Stone,
Gotham City University.
Yes. Here he is.
Victor Stone, star quarterback
for the Knight...
Shit, okay.
He's not Cyborg yet.
Wonder Woman.
Wonder Woman!
Las Vegas residency.
Illusions, juggling, and zebras.
No. That is not Diana.
- Aquaman.
- Aquaman?
Is that like a super mermaid?
No, Albert,
he's not a super mermaid.
Okay? He's half Atlantean,
half human
with superhuman strength who
can control marine life with his mind.
So, like a super mermaid?
No, Albert!
That is what you described.
We'll just try Arthur Curry...
Maine...
lighthouse.
Here we are. Thomas Curry.
That's his dad.
Uh, phone.
Hello.
- Hello, Thomas Curry?
- Yes.
Could I speak to Arthur?
Is Arthur around?
You wanna speak to my dog?
What? No, no. Um, sorry. Uh...
- Is this Thomas Curry?
- Yes.
- And you work at a lighthouse?
Okay, and your wife is
the queen of Atlantis?
- Will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
Uh, no.
Uh, right, but maybe, maybe...
um, a fish like woman
washed into your life
- at some point or another?
- Very funny, asshole.
Arthur Curry was never born.
- What?
- This is a disaster.
I-I-I completely
destroyed history.
Like Eric Stoltz.
Okay, why do you keep saying,
"Eric Stoltz"?
Eric Stoltz is Marty McFly.
- What?
- Time travel?
Oh. We talking "BTTF"?
Come on, who is this guy?
Okay, yeah, no, I know.
I've seen all of them
and Eric Stoltz
is not Marty McFly.
Really?
Then explain Marty McThigh here.
I can't explain that to you,
Gary.
That's not your thigh.
It's the wrong actor,
and it's upside down.
Is it?
The point is that
in Back to the Future
Marty McFly is very famously
played by Michael J. Fox.
The guy from Footloose?
No, that's Kevin Bacon!
- Bacon.
- Kevin Bacon's Maverick
with the volleyball,
the gay guys, and the planes?
- Top Gun.
- ♪ Great balls of fire! ♪
- Top Gun, right?
- No, no, no.
I completely broke the universe.
Marty McFly is Eric Stoltz.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
I created a world
with no met a humans.
And now there's no one
to defend us from Zod. Albert!
There's no Cyborg.
There's no Aquaman.
There's no Wonder Woman.
There's no Superman.
There's no Batman.
I'm Batman.
What, you...
What did you just say?
I'm Batman.
Batman exists?
- Hundo p.
- Yeah, dude.
Nobody knows who he really is,
- but he exists.
- Right.
Well, uh, we...
my cousin Barry and I,
have to go
to that cousin's dinner.
Now.
But it was a pleasure to meet
you all.
- And Gary.
- Barry.
- Gary.
Barry!
What, are you frickin'
kidding me with this place?
What is this, hell?
It's open.
- Look at all this cool shit!
- Okay, Barry, don't touch anything in here.
Hello?
Bruce?
♪ Waiting for
The break of day ♪
Bruce, are you there?
Oh, boy.
♪ Searching for
Something to say ♪
Hey, I didn't know you painted.
They're good.
Bruce Wayne?
Bruce?
Hey,
check this out. There's, like,
bells connected to every room
in this house.
Hey, maybe we can
find this Bruce guy...
if we just ring
all these bells, right?
You don't understand how servant
bells work? Those are all the bells.
- You ring them from all the other places.
- What?
You don't have, like,
Downton Abbey in your universe?
Downtown Abbey's?
The chain of, like,
family-style restaurants?
They're like,
it's like cheaper Bananabee's.
Oh, you know what
I'd really go for right now?
Abbey's sizzlin'
zucchini squares.
Okay.
You know what, man?
I've had it with you.
♪ Twenty five or six to four ♪
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy who lives here.
We're looking for Bruce Wayne.
You hungry?
Following the broadcast
earlier from General Zod.
The individual
they're searching for
- is still at large.
- So...
The president has yet to respond
to the broadcast from earlier,
and other foreign leaders
are said to be...
you're the same person as him...
- but from an alternate timeline.
- Yes.
In which...
you and I are friends?
Yeah, you're like
probably my best friend.
- Okay.
- Well, but you're a bit...
you're, uh...
- chronologically different.
- Older.
That's what I can't understand.
I traveled back in time
from here to here.
Yet somehow,
everything's all changed
back here.
- Or like when you were born, so...
- Well...
time isn't linear.
Right?
Right.
At some point
you probably saw a movie
that told you
that if you went back
and changed the past,
you'd create a kind of
a branched timeline, right?
Like, look.
New present
- and new future.
- Yeah.
Well, time doesn't
work like that.
That's not how time works.
When you go back
and change the past
you create a fulcrum.
You put yourself on a whole
nother strand of spaghetti.
New future. New past.
It's retrocausal.
It goes both ways.
Actually, it goes many ways.
Maybe some other time.
Okay, but in an ontological paradox model,
there's not...
What you did was
you changed the future
and you changed the past.
If a person
is stupid enough
to mess with time...
what you eventually
end up with is this.
The multiverse.
Some strands run
almost parallel.
There will be
inevitable intersections,
and others that are just...
wildly divergent.
What it is...
is a hot mess.
It's a crapshoot.
It's all just a crapshoot.
What does the parmesan mean?
The metaphor's over.
It's just a garnish.
And I'll tell ya something.
A person would have to be
an idiot
to play craps
with the space-time continuum.
Yeah, an idiot.
Here.
Mm.
Are you joking with
the chewing noises right now?
So, uh, you're the reason
this Zod character
is about to destroy the Earth?
Maybe.
There's a guy called Superman
who can stop Zod?
- Yeah, yeah.
- And flies?
Shoots lasers out of his eyes?
Yes, he flies, and he shoots
lasers out of his eyes. Yes.
No one said "Superman"...
that might be
a little on the nose?
- You call yourself Batman.
- Yeah.
I don't call myself
Super Batman.
Wait, he's Batman?
What did you think
we were doing here?
I thought this was
the cousin's dinner.
He's... Bruce Wayne is Batman?
Not really.
Not so much anymore.
You know...
they don't really need me.
Things have changed.
Gotham's now
one of the safest cities
in the world.
Well, I... I need you.
We need you.
In my timeline,
Batman's our strategist,
our leader.
The world needs Superman.
You're the best detective in the world.
You're probably the only person
who can help me find him.
So, will you help us?
Pass.
Like pass the salt?
Bruce?
He doesn't want to help us...
we're gonna use his bat shit.
Bat shit?
Yeah, his bat stuff,
his bat things.
Stand on that thing.
Okay, remember when you phased
through the floor?
- Yeah.
- So,
I need you to do that again.
Ow.
What is this place?
Dude!
This place straight beeves!
"Beeves"?
Barry!
I almost died
in an abyss!
12,805 Clark Kents in the US.
Is this what I think it is?
Holy shit!
I used to see this thing
on the news when I was a kid!
Okay, well...
refine search.
Date of birth.
- Wasn't born. He arrived.
- Oh!
Oh, Barry, look!
I'm busy.
With what?
Looking for unidentified objects
entering Earth's atmosphere
anywhere near Kansas
in the last 50 years.
He has a back door into NASA.
'Course he does.
Yeah, but Barry, check this out.
This bag laughs.
Okay, can't you
take anything seriously?
Stop messing around.
Dude, come on.
Have you seen this place?
It's amazing!
Hello!
Has the gravity of this
not sunk in for you?
Stop messing around, Barry.
I won't say it again.
Yeesh. Sorry, Mom.
Shut up. Shut up.
You have no idea
how lucky you are.
No idea!
You take everything for granted.
You don't even appreciate...
You just walk around
thinking that you're so funny
and so cool.
And it's embarrassing,
because you're not
any of those things!
Hey, screw you, man!
I've done nothing
but everything you've asked.
You made me
get struck by lightning!
I phased naked through the floor.
And I terrified Mrs. Johannson.
Now I'm probably
gonna have to move.
You won't even tell me
why you're here.
But will you at least tell me
why you're being so mean to me...
for no reason?
You used Monkey as a dartboard!
Wait, what?
Forget it.
The monkey? Wait...
So, you're mad at me
for playing with a toy?
It's not a toy.
Mom bought us that monkey.
'Cause she calls us Monkey.
She gives us monkey stuff
all the time.
Right.
Look...
I'm sorry.
I'm not very good with people.
Even myself.
Oh.
Come on, dude.
You're... You're not that bad.
You can just be kind of a dick
sometimes.
But let's face it.
I am pretty obnoxious.
But I just get excited.
Come on. This place
is pretty cool, right?
Yeah.
All right, well, um...
I'll let you work.
I know you're there.
You know what I'm stuck on?
That thing you said,
with the spaghetti.
You said there were certain intersections
that would always be inevitable.
You had an Alfred.
My Bruce has an Alfred.
Different worlds,
different times...
yet there it is.
Certain people,
certain events,
certain strands of spaghetti,
drawn to each other
like... like magnets.
I've read all about
temporal paradoxes
and causal loops.
But this is more than that.
Inevitable intersections
are something none of the theories
could have anticipated 'cause,
well, how do you explain that
except for...
fate?
If you are listening,
sorry about your parents.
I'm just trying to save mine.
There has to be a way.
There is a way, Barry.
Just keep trying.
Keep trying, Barry.
Found him.
Barry, wake up.
Clark's being held by a mercenary
group in a Siberian black site.
Get up, Barry.
The goat's on fire.
We're going to Russia.
Sweet.
Mm. Coffee.
How are we gonna get to Russia?
I'll help you get this Superman.
Then, you're on your own.
Oh!
You're...
You are, you're...
Yeah.
I'm Batman.
So, what's the plan?
We're just gonna, what,
grab Superman and dip set
before the block is hot?
I don't know.
Hey, you should ask him.
- You ask him.
- You should ask him.
Yeah, I'm not gonna ask him.
Why not? I thought Batman
was supposed to be your friend.
Not this one. Not this Batman.
- We're here.
- Activating hover mode.
- Ejector seat on.
- Ejector seat.
Ejector seat.
Okay, there are stages.
You're strapped
to your parachutes.
Hey, where's yours?
Whoo! This rips dicks!
All clear. Let's move.
Okay!
Good. Everybody's fast now
but me.
- Why is it so cold?
- It's the Arctic, Barry.
- Where'd he go?
- I don't know. Just follow the footprints.
Superman would be down there
for sure.
Yeah. Okay.
What did you do?
I had to move you.
But I just did it a little.
This might hurt.
Just let it out.
Let's go.
That's where you keep Superman.
Like a big scrotum.
He's gonna hack the Soviet security
cyberscrotum with a flip phone?
I tried all the combinations.
Yes!
Shit.
Kal-El?
It's not him.
We've gotta go.
Wait.
We can't just leave her here.
Look at her.
I'll grab her. Just go!
I got you.
I'll handle this jabroni.
What the...
Barry! Somebody shot me!
Time to dip set!
You, you lead the way!
- Go!
- Not that way! Not that way!
Oh, God!
Cover!
No!
It's coming around.
Hurry, hurry.
No, no, no! This is bullshit!
No!
Come on.
Let's go.
You didn't tell me
we could get shot!
Why would you assume
we couldn't?
Oh, great! To die
at the feet of a Sputnik.
Oh, man! I need this knee!
- Stay calm. It'll heal.
- Come on.
- How much do you weigh?
- 180.
Each. Plus her, 440.
Hold on.
Oh, great.
They're here.
They're over here, too.
Smirnoff Ice.
- Yes. Smirnoff Ice.
- Hi.
Stop them!
- Yep.
- Okay, they're serious. Barry, shut up.
Yeah, okay.
What's the play?
Batman, what do we do?
What now?
Now...
we try not to die.
Oh,
you guys should've seen that in slo-mo.
Yeah, I'm just realizing
that I didn't really think this through.
There are good Kryptonians...
and then there are very,
very bad Kryptonians.
And I was very confident
that we were just
gonna find Superman,
and if we found Superman,
then this would all be
super simple.
- Who are you?
- Holy Funyuns.
Hi.
- I... I'm Barry.
- We're Barry.
We were trying to find Kal-El.
But we found you instead.
What do you want with Kal-El?
We were trying to rescue him.
Why?
Because he's my friend.
Do you... Do you know him?
She looks mad. Get ready.
She might do laser vision,
or she might do, like, a freezy breath...
- or she'll just start throwing crazy...
- My name is Kara.
Daughter of Zor-El.
Kal-El was my cousin.
- Right, and who's Kal-El again?
- It's Superman.
- No, 'cause you said that was Clark.
- Who's Clark?
Clark is his human name.
Clark.
He was an infant when we left.
The last son of Krypton... I...
I was sent to protect him.
It looks like
he never made it to Earth
in this universe.
Our pods,
they must have separated.
Wait, so you thought a baby
was gonna protect us
from this Zod guy?
General Zod is here.
He must have tracked
my pod's signal.
- I have to go.
- Whoa, whoa, wait.
Well, you need to recover
your strength. Actually, Barry...
take her to the roof
and put her in the sun.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Whatever, like if, I mean,
you're solar powered.
Good for you.
I've been trying to...
Oh, uh...
We'll take that with us.
Um, am I cool to...
turn around?
Are you dressed
in a red cape?
You're levitating?
Is it always this loud?
Is it loud?
Are you, uh, good?
Do you feel, um...
strong yet, or...
Yep, that seems, uh,
seems strong. You know...
old man Barry, down there,
says if we don't stop
Captain Zode,
he'll kill thousands of people.
Billions of people.
Billions?
Of your people.
- They're good people.
- Good people?
We came to this planet
looking for
a safe place to live,
and they put me in a cage.
Yeah. A lot of humans
are dicks.
But then
there's babies and ballerinas.
And entertainment wrestlers.
A lot of humans
are worth saving.
Maybe to you.
But I'm not a human.
I'm a Kryptonian.
She's gone.
I have to get my powers back.
If I can re-create the accident
that gave me my powers...
maybe I can reconnect
to the Speed Force...
and maybe we'd stand a chance
against Zod.
Or kill yourself in the process.
Tell me something.
If you get your powers back,
you can go anywhere.
You can go to another timeline,
another universe.
Why do you wanna stay...
and fight to save this one?
Because this is the world
where my mom lives.
I went back in time to save her.
I'm not gonna lose her again.
The kid doesn't know, does he?
How do you tell someone
something like that?
I lost my parents...
but that pain...
made me who I am.
I'm not sure I know who I am
without it, actually.
I spent a lifetime...
trying to right
the wrongs of the past.
As if
putting on a cape
and fighting crime
would bring my parents back.
You actually did it.
So...
I guess the plan is
to douse yourself
in industrial chemicals
while electrocuting yourself?
Yep.
Want some help?
Hell yeah. That
would be incredibly useful.
I've actually already
borrowed some chemicals
and your soldering iron,
and I'm sitting
in your bat-seat.
Is that like a faux pas?
Wilco, Lima,
Zebra, be advised...
Air Command to Bravo 601.
Primary teams,
please confirm your AORs.
- Green teams ready to move.
- Standing by!
You bring me nothing? Hmm.
I gave you a warning.
Your failure to deliver
the Kryptonian traitor
is being taken as an act of war.
- Fire, fire, fire!
- We have contact, contact!
Weapons hot!
Weapons hot! Open fire!
No.
Air support now!
I repeat, air support!
Okay, when I throw the switch,
the current should
run up the wire
and draw the lightning
right to the kite.
Here, put that on.
It's heat and impact resistant.
Should protect you a little.
Right, but the point is
for me to not be protected.
Okay.
You're gonna need
to be out of the way.
I will.
Let's get electrocuted.
This is going to work, right?
Of course it's gonna work.
Nothing we haven't done before.
Besides, this time
we have Batman.
What could go wrong?
Uh, for the record,
I think this is insane.
Get back.
It's fine. It's fine.
Just you and me again,
Mr. Lightning.
Do it!
Wait, what? No!
No, wait! Stop! Stop!
Oh, God.
Barry, no.
Go again.
But...
Please.
The circuit is fried.
I've got you.
Hey. Barry.
You're okay.
It's like last time, right?
So, you gotta heal now.
Look, look, look!
It's working. It's working.
Yeah, it's working. Yeah.
Yeah,
he's healing. He's healing.
Oh, my God. He's okay.
Dude, you scared
the shit out of me.
You're awake.
How you feeling?
Slow.
Maybe this will help.
Ooh... Ooh!
Yes!
Dude, come on! Irresistible!
Man, feels good to be back.
Yeah!
And what are we wearing tonight?
You like it?
I-I made it myself
out of that old Batsuit.
But you know,
I made it our colors and everything.
Well, check this out!
It's a bit more loose.
It beeves.
Dude...
you really mean that?
I mean, I don't...
I don't know what it means,
exactly, to beeve.
But it seems like it's positive.
What are you doing?
You came back.
I'm glad you're okay.
I have to ask you something.
When you found me in that hole
that they put me in...
and I wasn't Kal-El...
why did you help me?
Because you needed help.
Do you know
what this symbol stands for?
- Supergirl?
- It means hope, right?
Hope, yeah. Does it mean hope?
Krypton was a beautiful place.
We are a people of hope,
not war.
I'm coming to you live
from Metropolis,
where minutes ago,
the mysterious flying...
Zod may be from Krypton,
but he is not my people.
So, you're saying...
Yes.
I will help you fight Zod.
Yes!
Interesting group.
What did you say, uh...
we were called again?
We're the Justice League.
No.
- No?
- Well, I mean, kinda.
We are short
one literal goddess...
one friendly Terminator
and super mermaid.
And we could
definitely use a Batman.
Are you in?
You wanna get nuts?
Let's get nuts.
In my world, Superman showed up
right away when Zod called him out.
So, as of now,
we're in uncharted territory.
What I do know is that Zod
somehow controls the World Engines,
which will be destroying
much more
than just Metropolis now
with every passing second
that we don't stop him.
Barry, what are you doing?
What?
Our kids are gonna
wanna see this.
Your kids?
Well, you know, like everybody's
kids. I mean, the children of the world.
They're gonna wanna see this.
We're getting close.
I'm gonna stay airborne
and take out their sky power.
And Barry, just so we're clear
what that essentially equates
to is you and me
versus the entire
Kryptonian army.
Chill.
We need to buy Kara enough time
to take out Zod.
Oh, and remember that your suit
doesn't dissipate energy like mine
so you need to take breaks,
otherwise you're gonna build up
too much charge.
Wait, what?
Dang it!
Hold on!
- Okay!
- Hold on.
The humans we came to protect?
They don't know
we're on their side.
Zod.
Kara Zor-El.
We've been waiting for you.
Go, go!
Cover!
- Drag him out, drag him!
- You go! I'll cover!
Okay, and the space giant...
and Mistress Murder...
- are our responsibility, too?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Don't think about them, okay?
Calm down.
We're just gonna start
with those guys over there.
And yeah, they're Kryptonian,
and we won't be able to kill them,
but we can slow them down
for her.
One at a time.
Okay? I'm gonna disarm them,
and then you'll engage.
Punch 'em.
Come on, Barbie.
Let's go party?
Okay, ow!
Oh.
Okay. It's okay.
You're okay. Come on.
Jesus, they're fast.
Yes, but not as fast as us.
Terraforming has begun.
This world must die
so that ours may live again.
Oh, my God. We gotta go.
We gotta go.
Dan, Danny, go, go!
Krypton is gone, Zod.
Your uncle...
Jor-El...
hid the key
to Krypton's rebirth
inside a Kryptonian child.
All the genetic material needed
to start again
coded inside the DNA,
then sent to Earth
in an escape pod.
He's not here. You have failed.
We found him.
We intercepted his pod.
But your cousin was
not the one we needed.
You are the one.
Kara Zor-El.
It is your blood...
we must harvest.
What did you do to Kal-El?
Your sacrifice that will allow
Krypton to live again.
What did you do?
The infant did not survive.
Look, new plan.
I'm gonna create
a cyclonic diversion.
And you're gonna
just come in, hard.
Feet first this time.
Yes!
Barry, did you see that?
Be careful. You're accumulating
too much charge.
What if I just Emperor this guy?
No, no, no!
Barry, that was actually
only half stupid!
But if you're gonna do that
and not die,
you need to complete
the circuit somehow.
Try putting
your hands together, like this.
Oh, shit.
- You're ready.
- Let's go!
♪ I seem to think I think
I got a little situation ♪
♪ So listen to me, sister
Listen maybe you can help ♪
♪ I think I gave a lot of
Problems my consideration ♪
♪ But not for me It always
seem to be For someone else ♪
♪ Why all the people always
Seem to just be on vacation ♪
♪ What do I get from it
I don't get anything at all ♪
♪ I'm like a trash can
Holding all the information ♪
♪ And every single time It
leaves me Feeling two feet tall ♪
♪ And only one I'm taking ♪
I'm going after the big one.
I've been hit.
Bruce, do you copy?
- Where's Kara?
- You go find her.
Bruce!
Ejection mode failure.
Rest, Kara Zor-El.
Going down.
But I'm not going alone.
No, no, no, Bruce!
Bruce, eject! Bruce,
just eject...
No!
Kara.
Isn't supposed...
Not supposed to happen...
Kara's dead.
They're both dead.
But they don't have to be,
right?
'Cause we can go back.
- Like you did.
- You're not fast enough yet.
You sure?
Barry!
Barry, wait!
Is this back enough?
Yeah, I guess so.
Listen, Barry, I...
What? It's okay.
We can fix this.
You know what
you're gonna change?
I know what I'm gonna change.
I'm going after the big one.
Bruce, pull off. That gunship
is shield-protected.
Roger that.
Bet he's not.
Who? Space giant?
Yes, yes, please take him out.
Yes.
No.
Hey.
It'll be okay.
Not this time, kid.
Maybe some other time.
We can't bring you back, can we?
You already did.
Come on, Barry.
Gotta get up. Come on.
- Barry.
- We go again.
Barry.
Let's just go.
Barry, come on. Let's just go.
Barry, there's no point.
Barry!
Phase!
Okay, I have to pull it out.
- I have to pull it out.
- No, I'm okay.
You have to phase again.
Barry, phase again.
I'm okay. I just
should've stopped sooner.
Ow!
Again.
Barry.
Okay, can we please
just take a minute?
Sorry, dude.
Yeah, bro, of course.
That's the whole thing.
We can take as much time
as it takes.
No, that's not what I mean.
Hey!
Okay, you good? Come on.
I need you in there. Let's go.
Barry, please,
just listen to me!
Where were you?
What, you just stand here
the whole time?
Barry, this is
an inevitable intersection.
You have to stop. Barry!
No, Barry, wait!
Barry, listen.
There's something
I should tell you.
I went back in time initially
- because...
- Yeah, because Mom died.
How do you know?
It doesn't matter. Does it?
You know that I have to
undo what I did.
No.
It's not a mistake.
We can save her.
And we can save them.
No, we can't.
This is what
Bruce was talking about.
Barry, this is inevitable.
We can try a million times,
and we're not gonna be able to fix this.
No matter what we do...
this world dies.
Today.
Look around.
Look at the damage
we're causing.
Now we have to stop.
Okay?
Look, I was just
doing my laundry.
You're the one who came and
told me that I'm a superhero.
And now you're saying what?
You don't want me to be?
Well, guess what!
It's too late!
I am...
The Flash.
And I can save everyone.
Nobody dies!
Barry...
not every problem
has a solution.
Not every problem
Sometimes we just
have to let go.
Sometimes you just
Let go of Mom?
She'll always be alive,
somewhere in time.
Always.
Just not for us.
You're full of shit, dude.
I'm going back.
You're going back to kill Mom?
No!
You're staying!
You stay, right here.
Just give me one more time.
Barry, stop!
You, stop!
Feel like we got off
on the wrong foot.
Let's start again.
I'm the Flash.
What's your name?
I've lived...
more than you can dream.
Not an answer.
Do you, like, rehearse that?
Whoa.
Get out of here, Barry!
That scar, you...
Oh, my God.
So, you're... You are...
Yes, I am...
you.
We are so close.
I've got it almost figured out.
How long
have you been doing this?
Time is inconsequential.
Come on, Barry.
Up in the sky!
It's a bird!
It's a plane!
It's Superman!
Purrfectly foolproof.
Only the
Joker would think of that.
Please just look at
what's happening.
These worlds...
They're colliding
and collapsing.
We did this.
W-We're destroying
the fabric of everything.
You have to stop.
It stops once I've fixed it!
It's not entirely your fault,
Barry.
I pushed you out of the
Chronobowl on that September 29
so you could start me
on this path. Hmm?
How do you like
our endless paradox?
I made you create me...
and now you're the one...
in my way.
No matter how close I get
to winning this fight...
you go back
and let Mom die.
You're the inevitable
intersection.
And you do have to let go.
What's he talking about?
You're my hero.
What did you do?
Hey, hey. Don't worry.
It's gonna heal.
I just wanted to...
You tell Mom I love her.
Don't forget the tomatoes.
I used to love that cereal
when I was a kid.
Yeah.
My son goes nuts for it.
They stop making it.
Well, I know they
were talking about discontinuing it.
- Do I know you?
- No, I'm not from around here.
I was just visiting my mom.
Maybe I know her.
What's her name?
She's the best...
and kindest person in the world.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just...
I'm really gonna miss her.
I know I'm just...
a random lady in a store.
But do you want a hug?
Mm-hmm. Sure.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, don't say that.
Your mom must be grateful
you came to visit her.
She's very lucky to have you.
I'm very lucky to have her.
Ah! You have to tell her that.
Moms like to hear
these kind of things.
Believe me.
Love you, Mom.
I love you more.
I loved you first.
Bye.
I'm back.
Shit!
Court!
Original trial was initially...
I'm so sorry.
As I was saying...
the same
security camera footage,
Exhibit F in the original trial,
was initially
considered useless,
but has now
been enhanced,
using the latest tech
from Wayne Enterprises.
It confirms
the alibi
Mr. Allen has argued,
and his son, Barry,
has corroborated, since day one.
Here.
Right here, you can clearly see
my client, Mr. Allen,
reaching for a can of tomatoes
on the top shelf.
Mr. Allen, Mr. Allen, can you tell us a
bit more about what happened, please?
Well, um...
the tomatoes moved from
the bottom shelf to the top shelf,
and subsequently,
uncooked the spaghetti.
Unquote.
I'm sorry, that makes absolutely no
sense. What are you talking about, sir?
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- The allegations, the trial...
We're good here. Thank you.
Statement in the court.
- Did I give a good quote?
- Yeah.
Spaghetti.
Hey, speaking of food,
I was thinking, um...
you should ask me to dinner.
D-Dinner with me?
Yes, a date, Barry.
Iris West,
do you wanna dinner-date me?
- I'd love to.
- Thank you.
I'd love to also.
Call me.
- Bruce!
- Congratulations.
Thank you. You have no idea
how good it is to hear your voice.
I... I have so much to tell you the next
time I see you, Bruce. You were right.
Okay? And I didn't listen.
And things did get very,
very weird,
but I put everything back,
I promise.
I'm pulling up now.
Oh, great.
- Get the shot.
- Sir, sir!
- Back up, please.
- Shot!
Sir, I'd like to ask
you for a video for the Daily Planet.
- Wayne! Wayne!
- Step aside.
Was it backed by
your own allegation?
Who the fuck is this?
He's not
answering any questions.
Hey, Barry.
No, wh-where's...
You're, you... No.
You can't...
You... You're not Batman.
What's wrong with you?
Huh.
Well...
♪ Let it go ♪
♪ This too shall pass ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
♪ You can't keep lettin' it
Get you down ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
♪ You can't keep lettin' it
Get you down ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
♪ You can't keep lettin' it
Get you down ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
♪ You can't keep lettin' it
Get you down ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
♪ You can't keep lettin' it
Get you down ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
♪ You can't keep lettin' it
Get you down ♪
♪ When the morning comes ♪
I've told you
it's my metabolism, right?
I can't get drunk.
I can't get drink either.
Listen. Listen, I'm,
'cause I'm trying to... No, no, no.
'Cause what I'm trying to explain as
simply as I possibly can, I promise...
They were all Batman.
They were all Bruce Wayne.
But each of them was
a completely different person.
- So, on the other line-time...
- Timeline.
I'm the same guy?
Yeah. Actually, pretty much.
You're lovable, furry...
loyal, motivated by bacon.
All right, listen.
Thank you for making it more
simpler for me, Mr. Simple More.
Yeah, I'm doing my best.-
Look, you're missing
the larger premise here.
In my timeline, when I...
All right, come on.
Up, up, Broseidon.
I thought you were gonna
sleep on the couch.
Arthur, I live right here.
Harry?
I live right here. It's okay.
Okay.
Oh, hey.
More beer.
Go fast. Oh, here! Here.
Here. Pay with this.
Arthur,
this is Atlantean treasure.
You... You tell them that.
♪ Got no money
For the sailor suit I... ♪
- Yep.
- ♪ I'm a sailor... ♪
You're a sailor.
He's fine.